SeHee Son

San Francisco, CA | seheesf88@gmail.com | (415) 728-2420

http://linkedin.com/in/sehee-son/ | https://git.generalassemb.ly/seheesf88/ | https://portfolio-sehee-v2.herokuapp.com/

Summary

I am highly self-motivated junior software engineer that loves to learn code. I have worked in the hospitality industry and medical fields for 10 years and have gained various experiences and skills in how to work in part of team and in a fast-paced work environment. I strongly believe that I can perform amazing work by dedicating my professional technics and experiences.

Skills & Tools

Languages & frameworks JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, Node.js, React.js, Flask, EJS, JSX, Ajax, Jinja, Oauth-passport Database mongoDB, Mongoose, SQLite, Postgresql, API

Methodologies MVC pattern, CRUD pattern, REST architecture

Management & deployment & Tools Git, Github, Command Line, Mocha, Heroku, Atom, Postman, Moqups

Human language skills: in Korean: NATIVE | Japanese: Advanced

Projects

Trip Planner (Concept Project) [Git] [Application]

Mar 2019

- The application what a user can use to plan and manage a trip budget and itinerary.
- Tech: JavaScript, React.js, JSX, Ajax, mongoDB, mongoose, RESTful Api, CRUD pattern, CSS.

SeeStar (Concept Project) [Git] [Application]

Feb 2019 – Mar 2019

• A clone of Instagram app. The user can post and share their pictures and stories and view other user's pictures and story. Tech: Java Script, Python, React.js, Flask, Postgresql, RESTful Api, CRUD pattern JSX, Ajax, CSS.

Flight Tracker (Concept Project [Git] [Application]

Feb 2019

- The application for a user to track flights and share reports about delays.
- Tech: Java Script, React.js, JSX, Ajax, mongoDB, Mongoose, RESTful Api, CRUD pattern, CSS.

Work Experience

Barista, Starbucks, San Francisco, CA

Nov 2017 - Present

- Responsible for communicates effectively with a team to provide quality beverages, whole bean, and food products to customers in fast paced environment.
- Complied with standards for merchandising, stocking, and storing products

Lead Receptionist, Myoung Lee, D.D.S., San Francisco, CA

Dec 2014 - Sep 2018

- Making appointments over the phone and in person. Verifying insurance eligibility and benefits and billing, collecting payment from patients or their insurance. Staffing and Training new employees and assigning tasks.
- Taking x-rays, organize charts

Dental Assistant, Myoung Lee, D.D.S., San Francisco, CA

Dec 2014 – Sep 2018

Customer Service Agent, Frontier Airline, San Francisco, CA

Mar 2015 - July 2015

- Checking-in passengers and luggage at the ticketing counter.
- Providing gate service including paging passengers and assisting boarding procedure including arranging seats per clients' requests and per plane regulation.

Intern, Portal World Travel, San Francisco, CA

Jan 2012 - Dec 2012

- Assisting superior by planning itinerary and researching local area and amenities.
- Researching price of hotels, flights, and rental cars and making reservation.

Education

General Assembly

Dec 2018 - Mar 2019

Software Engineering Immersive (formerly Web Development Immersive)

San Francisco State University (SFSU) - Cum Laude

2014

Bachelor of Art in Japanese Language and Literature (BA)

City College of San Francisco (CCSF)

2012

Associate in Science Degree in Travel and Tourism Management (AS)

Portfolio



Linkedin

